[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which of these is not a wild animal ?",
        "a": "Goat",
        "b": "Lion",
        "c": "Bear",
        "d": "Leopard",
        "e": "Tiger",
        "answer": "Goat"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which of these is a fruit ?",
        "a": "Apple Cidar",
        "b": "Egg",
        "c": "Yam",
        "d": "Orange",
        "e": "Fish",
        "answer": "orange"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "The Correct Answer is D",
        "a": "incorrect",
        "b": "Incorrect",
        "c": "Incorrect",
        "d": "Correct",
        "e": "Incorrect",
        "answer": "Correct"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which of these is not a wild animal ?",
        "a": "Goat",
        "b": "Lion",
        "c": "Bear",
        "d": "Leopard",
        "e": "Tiger",
        "answer": "Goat"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which of these is a fruit ?",
        "a": "Apple Cidar",
        "b": "Egg",
        "c": "Yam",
        "d": "Orange",
        "e": "Fish",
        "answer": "Orange"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The Correct Answer is D",
        "a": "incorrect",
        "b": "Incorrect",
        "c": "Incorrect",
        "d": "Correct",
        "e": "Incorrect",
        "answer": "Correct"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which of these is not a wild animal ?",
        "a": "Goat",
        "b": "Lion",
        "c": "Bear",
        "d": "Leopard",
        "e": "Tiger",
        "answer": "Goat"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which of these is a fruit ?",
        "a": "Apple Cidar",
        "b": "Egg",
        "c": "Yam",
        "d": "Orange",
        "e": "Fish",
        "answer": "Orange"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The Correct Answer is D",
        "a": "incorrect",
        "b": "Incorrect",
        "c": "Incorrect",
        "d": "Correct",
        "e": "Incorrect",
        "answer": "Correct"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question": "Which of these is not a wild animal ?",
        "a": "Goat",
        "b": "Lion",
        "c": "Bear",
        "d": "Leopard",
        "e": "Tiger",
        "answer": "Goat"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which of these is a fruit ?",
        "a": "Apple Cidar",
        "b": "Egg",
        "c": "Yam",
        "d": "Orange",
        "e": "Fish",
        "answer": "Orange"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "The Correct Answer is D",
        "a": "incorrect",
        "b": "Incorrect",
        "c": "Incorrect",
        "d": "Correct",
        "e": "Incorrect",
        "answer": "Correct"
    },
 {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Which of these is a fruit ?",
        "a": "Apple Cidar",
        "b": "Egg",
        "c": "Yam",
        "d": "Orange",
        "e": "Fish",
        "answer": "Orange"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "The Correct Answer is D",
        "a": "incorrect",
        "b": "Incorrect",
        "c": "Incorrect",
        "d": "Correct",
        "e": "Incorrect",
        "answer": "Correct"
    }
]